{
    "subject": "resource/David_Fisher_(politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Ohio",
    "human_readable": "David Fisher's death place is Ohio.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8349550366401672,
            "question": "What state was David Fisher's death place in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7995744943618774,
            "question": "Where did David Fisher die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6613085865974426,
            "question": "Was David Fisher born in Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2719285786151886,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about David Fisher?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23256643116474152,
            "question": "Are there any notable people from Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15997231006622314,
            "question": "In which US state is Ohio located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11813358217477798,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10225584357976913,
            "question": "What is the capital of Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07908648252487183,
            "question": "What is the geography like in Ohio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.045860182493925095,
            "question": "Is Ohio known for any specific industries or products?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David Fisher's death place is Ohio.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3262_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geography like in Ohio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3262_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of Ohio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3262_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Ohio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3262_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3262_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text mentions that \"David \u201cDave\u201d L. Fisher of North Lima Road, Boardman, Ohio\" passed away, which implies that he died in Ohio."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention multiple individuals named David Fisher who lived in or passed away in Ohio. Specifically, the document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3262/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt` states \"FISHER David \u201cDave\u201d L., 80, North Lima Road, Boardman, Ohio.\" and another document at path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3262/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt` mentions the death of \"Bruce David Fisher, 87, of Grove City, Ohio,\" indicating that David Fisher's death place is in Ohio."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}